A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Program Division, Office of the Vice President, Office Files of James H. Lapple FA599
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program Reviews and Budgets, 1987-1994; 1; 5.39 Cubic Feet 13 containers
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Office of the Vice President (OVP) and United States and International Affairs Program (USIAP) and Developing Countries Program (DCP) Grants Administration, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Urban Poverty (120), 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Human Rights and Governance (130), 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - International Affairs Program (140) (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Education and Culture (150), 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Rural Poverty and Resources (170) (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - PRI (610), 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Asia (230), 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Africa and the Middle East (240), 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Cost Center Budget Report FY 1990 - Latin America and the Caribbean (250) (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Ford Foundation Program Division - March 1990 Budget Review, 1990 March (Box 10, Folder 120)
  - Budget Fiscal Year 1991 - 110/205, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 121, Box 11, Folder 122)
  - United States and International Affairs Program (USIAP) Program Review, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 123-125)
  - Quarterly Budget Project Fiscal Year 1991, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 126-127)
  - James Lapple Memoranda, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 128-130)
  - Miscellaneous Reports Re:Brand Quality, Debt Conversion, Etc. (For Class?), 1988 (Box 12, Folder 131)
- Field Office Files, 1971-1997; 2; 7.96 Cubic Feet 21 containers
  This series details the management and operations of Foundation offices abroad and includes interoffice memoranda, employment contracts, property leases, country agreements, consultant's reports, meeting and site visit materials, and handwritten notes. The bulk of the files focus on the Foundation's developing interests in Namibia and Chile, documenting both the establishment of offices within the two countries and the redistribution of responsibilities of former regional branches. Records in this series also chart Mr. Lapple's Beijing, Cairo, and Lima office visits to supervise the installation of the FOGS software and the development of the protocols governing its use.
  - Africa and the Middle East (AME) - Namibia - Establishment of Field Office - Country Agreement and Memoranda Re: Employment Policies, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Africa and the Middle East (AME) - Namibia - South Africa/Namibia Task Force Visit (July 1992) - Agenda and Hotel Reservation Information, 1992 June-July (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Africa and the Middle East (AME) - West Africa - Report, "Funds for Community Development Associations (FCDAs)" by the Ford Foundation, West Africa Office - Report 012438, 1990 March (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Africa and the Middle East (AME) - West Africa (Nigeria) - Office Space - Property Lease, 1990 April (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - ASIA (Asia and the Pacific) - Bangladesh - Office Space - Memoranda, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - ASIA (Asia and the Pacific) - Bangladesh - Office Space - Floor Plans, 1991 (Folder 344)
  - ASIA - China - Field Office Grant System (FOGS) Installation - Agendas, Memoranda, Grant Reports, 1991 June-December (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - ASIA - India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka - Office Lease Agreement, 1991 February-June (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - ASIA - Southeast Asia (Indonesia) - Office Lease Agreement, 1991 January-February (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Lima) - Field Office Grant System (FOGS) Installation - Agenda, Memoranda, Survey, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Lima) - Regional Office Staffing and Transition to Sub-Office Status, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago) - Andrew Wallace Consultancy - Memoranda, Consultant's Reports, 1990 May-September (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago) - Employment Contracts and Memoranda Re: Field Office Staffing, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago) - Employment Surveys (Salary and Benefits) and Correspondence - Price Waterhouse and Langton Clark, 1990 December-1991 April (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago) - Legal Fees and Attorney Contracts Re: Work Rendered in 1990, 1990 October - 1991 February (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago) - Legal Work Re: Establishment of Field Office in Chile, 1971-1991 (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago) - Meetings and Site Visits - Agendas, Meeting Materials, Discussion Topics, Notes Re: Establishment and Staffing of Regional Office in Chile, 1990 April - 1991 January (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago) - Office Space - Memoranda, Correspondence, Lease Agreements Re: Santiago Rentals and Renovations, 1990 January - 1991 January (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Santiago and Lima) - Expenditure Issues and Observations - Budget Reports, Memoranda, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Africa and the Middle East (AME) Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - AME - Eastern and Southern Africa (Kenya) Office Budget Report (with accompanying documents including office leases), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - AME - Eastern and Southern Africa (Zimbabwe) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - AME - North Africa and Middle East (Egypt) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - AME - North Africa and Middle East (Sudan) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - AME - South Africa and Namibia Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - AME - West Africa (Nigeria) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - AME - West Africa (Senegal) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Asia and the Pacific (ASIA) Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - ASIA - Bangladesh Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - ASIA - China Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - ASIA - India Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - ASIA - Southeast Asia (Indonesia) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - ASIA - Southeast Asia (Philippines) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - ASIA - Southeast Asia (Thailand) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Latin America and the Caribbean (LAC) Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - LAC - Andean Region and the Southern Cone (Peru) Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - LAC - Brazil Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - LAC - Mexico Office Budget Report, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - Namibia - Salary Survey Engagement Letters and Recruiting Engagement Letters, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - Namibia - Task Force General Notes, undated (Box 14, Folder 170)
  - Namibia - Newspaper Clippings, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 171)
  - Namibia - Administrative Files, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 172-174)
    Memos, Personnel Policy and Practices Manual, correspondence regarding Namibian National Salary Survey, Namibia Task Force Draft, Field Office Timetable, Task Force Meeting Agendas, job descriptions and office hierarchy, drafts, Republic of Namibia National Assembly Labour Bill B.42 - '91,
  - Accountant CVs - Jobs Unlimited, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 341)
    Restricted
  - Namibia Agreement, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - An Evaluation of Current Renumeration Practices and Market Rates in Namibia, Price Waterhouse Meyernel (2 copies), 1992 March (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Namibia/South Africa Visit, 1992 July (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Namibia - Start-Up Visit, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Capital Project - Jakarta - Proposed New Field Office Building, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Capital Projects - Andean Region and the Southern Cone - Budget File, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 180)
  - Andean Regional and the Southern Cone - Lima Office Memos, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 181)
  - Chile - Santiago Personnel Policy and Practices Manual, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 182)
  - Chile - Salary Report prepared by Langton Clarke and Annual Reporting to Ministry of Justice, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 183)
  - Chile - Personnel Policies, Lease Agreements (for office), etc., 1991 (Box 15, Folder 184)
  - Chile-Lima Transition - Lima Severance Issues, Accounting Arrangements, Personnel Policy, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Field Office Delegations of Authority, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Field Office Local Delegations of Authority - Correspondence, Memoranda, Reports, 1989-1993 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Field Office Grants System (FOGS) - Cairo - Installation, Use, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Field Office Grants System (FOGS) - Brazil - Installation, Use, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 189)
  - Field Office Grants System (FOGS) - Bangladesh - Dhaka Office - Installation, Use, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 190)
  - Pending Travel - Office of Management Services, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 191)
  - Santiago Visit, 1994 March 14-19 (Box 17, Folder 192-194)
  - Summary of Risk Management Program for Field Offices, 1991 May (Box 17, Folder 195)
  - Thailand Provident Fund, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 196)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - Cairo/Dakar, 1992 September 21-October 2 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - South Africa Recruiting Firms/Namibia Training, 1992 December (Box 18, Folder 198)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - South Africa, 1993 February-March (Box 18, Folder 199)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - South Africa, 1993 September (Box 18, Folder 200)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - South Africa, 1993 April (Box 18, Folder 201)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - Namibia, 1992 July (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - Nigeria Visit, 1993 October (Box 18, Folder 203)
  - Field Office Notebook - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 204)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - General Meeting Notes, undated (Box 18, Folder 205)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - Nigeria Visit, 1990 February (Box 18, Folder 206)
  - Field Office Visit Notebook - Santiago Visit, 1990 November (Box 18, Folder 207)
  - Kenya Trip, 1986 August (Box 19, Folder 208)
  - Southeast Asia Trip, 1986 December (Box 19, Folder 209)
  - Southeast Asia Trip - Thailand, 1986 December (Box 19, Folder 210)
  - Southeast Asia Trip - Manila, 1986 December (Box 19, Folder 211)
  - Southeast Asia Trip - Trip Report, 1987 Jan 21 (Box 19, Folder 212)
  - Southeast Asia Trip - Thank You Notes, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 213)
  - Mexico Trip - Mexico City Field Office Accounting, Administrative Policies, New Personnel, Budget Information, etc., 1985-1987 (Box 19, Folder 214)
  - Mexico Trip - Preliminary Agenda, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 215)
  - Cairo Implementation - Agenda, 1987 June (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Cairo Implementation - Ariela's Report - Egypt #1, 1987 June 10; 5.25" floppy disk (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Cairo Implementation - Ariela's Report - Egypt #2, 1987 June 10; 5.25" floppy disk (Box 19, Folder 216)
  - Cairo Implementation - Trip Report, 1987 July 13 (Box 19, Folder 217)
  - Cairo Implementation - Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 218)
  - Brazil Implementation - Pre-Implementation Memo and Subject Category Codes, 1987 August (Box 19, Folder 219)
  - Brazil Implementation - Agenda, 1987 August (Box 19, Folder 220)
  - West Africa Trip - Lagos, 1987 September (Box 20, Folder 221)
  - West Africa Trip - Senegal Follow-Up Request, 1988 March 22 (Box 20, Folder 222)
  - West Africa Trip - Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 223)
  - Mexico Implementation - Pre-Implementation Memo, 1988 January 12 (Box 20, Folder 224)
  - Mexico Implementation - Agenda, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 225)
  - Mexico Implementation - Trip Report, 1988 March 22 (Box 20, Folder 226)
  - Jakarta Pre-Implementation, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 227)
  - China Field Visit, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 228)
  - China Field Visit - Agenda, 1988 May (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Beijing, 1988; 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Beijing, 1988; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - China Agenda, 1988; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 229)
  - Kenya Implementation - Pre-Implementation Memo, 1988 April 25 (Box 20, Folder 230)
  - Kenya Implementation - Implementation Report, 1988 June 24 (Box 20, Folder 231)
  - Kenya Implementation - Kenya Programming Changes Memo, 1988 April 14 (Box 20, Folder 232)
  - Kenya Implementation - Miscellaneous Memoranda and Materials, 1988 June (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Kenya Program 1, 1988; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Kenya Data 1, 1988; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Kenya Program 2, 1988; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Kenya Data 2, 1988; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Kenya, 1988; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 20, Folder 233)
  - Southeast Asia Installation - Pre-Implementation Memo - Bangkok, 1988 June 23 (Box 20, Folder 234)
  - Southeast Asia Installation - Pre-Implementation Memo - Jakarta, 1988 June 23 (Box 20, Folder 235)
  - Southeast Asia Installation - Pre-Implementation Memo - Manila, 1988 June 23 (Box 20, Folder 236)
  - Southeast Asia Installation - Pre-Implementation Trip Report/Sample Report Index, 1988 March 23 (Box 20, Folder 237)
  - Southeast Asia Installation - Bangkok/Manila Changes, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 238)
  - Southeast Asia Installation - Field Office Budget Submissions Fiscal Year 1989, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 239)
  - Southeast Asia Installation - Accounting Software Implementation Memos, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 240)
  - Bangladesh/India Visit - Agenda and Handwritten Notes, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 241)
  - Bangladesh/India Visit - Bangladesh Visit, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 242)
  - Bangladesh/India Visit - India Visit, 1986-1989 (Box 21, Folder 243)
  - Kenya Modification Visit - Agenda, 1989 March (Box 21, Folder 244)
  - Kenya Modification Visit - Trip Report and Trip-Related Memoranda and Notes, 1988 November - 1989 March (Box 21, Folder 245)
  - Senegal Financial Accounting Software Installation, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 246)
  - Backup Senegal Bank - RGC Directory Using Copy, 1989; 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 246)
  - Backup Senegal Main Directory and Budget Using Copy, 1989; 3.5 inch floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 246)
  - Peru Installation, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 247)
  - Peru FA Progress and Data Back-Up, 1989 October 21; 5.25" floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 247)
  - China Installation, 1989 November (Box 21, Folder 248)
  - Financial Accounting System Complete Back-Up - 01, 1989 November; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 248)
  - Financial Accounting System Complete Back-Up - 02, 1989 November; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 248)
  - Financial Accounting System Complete Back-Up - 003, 1989 November; 5.25" floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 248)
  - Full Back-Up of Inventory/China Office, 1989 November; 5.25 inch floppy disk (Box 21, Folder 248)
  - Kenya/Nairobi/Harare Installation Visit, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 249)
  - India/Egypt Trip, 1988-1990 (Box 22, Folder 250)
  - Indonesia Version - Financial Accounting Software, User's Manual, undated (Box 22, Folder 251)
  - Bangkok Field Office Administration Manual and Materials, 1977-1995 (Box 22, Folder 252)
    Personnel Policies
    Administrative Procedures
    Trip Reports
  - Bangladesh Field Office Administration Manual and Materials, 1981-1997 (Box 22, Folder 253)
  - Developing Countries Program - Fiscal Year 1987 - Administration and Accounting Meeting - Discussion Materials, Prepared by Office of the Secretary, 1986 October 21 (Box 22, Folder 254)
  - Field Office Accounting Conference - Developing Country Program - Admin and Accounting Meeting, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 255)
  - Field Office Accounting Conference - Invitation Lists and Agenda, 1986 October (Box 23, Folder 256)
  - Field Office Accounting Conference - Detailed Agenda, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 257)
  - Field Office Accounting Conference - Individual Grants, 1986 October (Box 23, Folder 258)
  - Field Office Accounting Conference - Memos to Field Office Representatives, 1986 November (Box 23, Folder 259)
  - Field Office Accounting Conference - Overseas Transaction Journal Logistical Review, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 260)
  - Field Office Accounting Conference - The Role of the Investment Division, 1986 October (Box 23, Folder 261)
  - Field Office Administration - Accounting Practices and Procedures and Foreign Currency Memo, 1986 March 10 (Box 23, Folder 262)
  - Field Office Administration - Organizational Charts for Field Offices, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 263)
  - Field Office Administration - Names and Addresses (of Representatives), 1987 January (Box 23, Folder 264)
  - Field Office Administration - Overseas Grant Payment Memo, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 265)
  - Field Office Administration - 1987 Program Review (Box 23, Folder 266)
  - Field Office Administration - 1988 Budget Instructions, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 267)
  - Field Office Administration - Program Review Fiscal Year 1989, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 268)
  - Field Office Administration - MIS (Management Information System?) Support for Field Offices Memo, 1988 July 20 (Box 23, Folder 269)
  - Field Office Administration - Budget Instructions, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 270)
  - Brazil and India Grants Systems, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 271)
  - Cairo Grants System, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 272)
  - China Grants System, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 273)
  - Indonesia Grants System, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 274)
  - Kenya Grants System, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 275)
  - Mexico Grants System, 1987-1990 (Box 24, Folder 276)
  - Peru Grants System, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 277)
  - Field Office Grants System - Overview, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 278)
    Overviews for China, India, Indonesia, Kenya, Mexico, Peru, Senegal
  - Field Office Grants System - Memos, Project Timetables, and Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 279)
  - Field Office Grants System - Notes, undated (Box 24, Folder 280)
  - Field Office Grants System - Grants Administrator Survey and Responses, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 281)
  - Graphics Software Demonstration, undated (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - Field Office Grants System - Installation Schedule Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 283)
  - Field Office Grants System - Responses - Design Document, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 284)
  - Field Office Grants System - Overview Documents, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 285)
  - Field Office Grants System - Data Dictionary, undated (Box 25, Folder 286)
  - Field Office Grants System - Grantee Profile Data, Field Office Automation Project Feasibility Study, and Design Documents, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 287)
  - Field Office Grants System - India, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 288)
  - Field Office Grants System - Installation, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 289)
  - Capital Projects, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 290, Box 26, Folder 291)
    India, Chile, Indonesia, Bangladesh, Namibia, South Africa
  - Training Issues, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 292)
  - Introduction to Personal Computers for the Ford Foundation, Student Manual, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 293)
  - The Ford Foundation Developing Country Program FY 1993 Budget Submission (Box 26, Folder 294-295)
  - Delhi, India - Asia Regional Meetings (primarily February 12-20, 1994 but also January 18-27, 1995), 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 296)
  - Chika Iritani and New Delhi Correspondence, 1986-1996 (Box 26, Folder 297)
  - Delhi Electrical Upgrade, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 298)
  - New Delhi, India Office Files, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 299-300)
  - New Delhi Office Internal Learning Report, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - India - Procedures Manual Outline, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 302)
  - India - 40 Years Publication Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 303)
  - India - Field Office Personnel Manual (India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka), 1983-1991 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - India - Office Renovations and Delegation of Authority Documents, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 305)
  - India - Tribute to F.C. Bhambri, Asia Regional Meeting, 1994 February 2 (Box 27, Folder 306)
  - India - Retirement Letters for P. Subbiah and K. Venkataraman, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 307)
  - India - An Evaluation of the Post-Doctoral Research Fellowships Program in Economics, I.G. Patel, 1994 September (Box 27, Folder 308)
  - India - Administrative Procedures, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - India - Field Office Audits, 1992-1997 (Box 27, Folder 310)
  - India - Evaluations and Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 311)
  - India - Joint Forest Management in India: Regenerating and Managing Degraded Natural Forests in Partnership with Local Communities, Jeffrey Y. Campbell, undated (Box 28, Folder 312)
  - India - Franklin Thomas Speech 40th Anniversary of Delhi Office, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - Franklin Thomas Trip Sri Lanka (May 1-6, 1993), 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - Vietnam Office Files, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 315-316)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Ford Foundation Activities in Vietnam Report, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Vietnam and the Ford Foundation, Trustees Meeting, 1994 June (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Administrative Files and Opening of Hanoi Office, 1993-1996 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Regulations of Non-governmental Organizations in Vietnam, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Charles Benoit, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Staff Visits, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 322)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 323)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Trustees Meeting Report and Notes, 1994 June (Box 29, Folder 324)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Field Office Audits, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 325)
  - Vietnam Office Files - Administration, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Vietnam Office Files - The Ford Foundation Field Office Administrative Procedure, Hanoi Office, 1997 July (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Grants Classification System - Subject Coding, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 328-329, Box 30, Folder 330)
  - Namibia Office Files - Administration, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 331)
  - Namibia Office Files - Rossing Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 332)
  - Namibia Office Files - Administrative Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 333)
  - Namibia Office Files - Government Gazette of the Republic of Namibia, 1992 April 8 (Box 30, Folder 334)
  - Namibia Office Files - General, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 342)
    Restricted - Personnel File
  - Paris - Study Group on Exchange of Development Information (June 19-21, 1991) (Box 30, Folder 335-336)
  - MIS (Management Information System?) - General, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 337)
  - MIS (Management Information Systems) - Steering Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 31, Folder 338-339)
  - 1994 USIAP (United States International Affairs Program) Budgets, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 340)